怒火攻心
赫克托尔  开始录了吗?  好极了
Hector, are we spinning yet? Nice.
查略斯!  还好吗  宝贝儿?
Chelios! How we doing, baby?
你从不给我打电话
And you never call me no more.
怎么回事?  我们的情谊呢?
Come on' what is that? Where's the love?
你现在感觉怎么样?
How are you feeling?
我想你现在感觉糟透了
I guess you're feeling like shit' right about now.
现在你不能...
You can't...
移动不太方便吧  哈?
You can't move too good, huh?
呼吸也不太顺畅  怎么搞的呢?
You can't breathe too good. What's wrong with you?
等等  等等!  这是什么?
Wait' wait, wait' wait! What is this?
啊  操!
Oh' fuck!
猜猜看这是什么?  我打赌你会知道的  查略斯
Can you guess what this is? I bet you can, Chelios.
坚持住  来看看这个
Hold on' check this out.
啊!  这真是太变态了  伙计!
Oh! This is plain sick, man!
我真是变态中的天才啊!
I must be the motherfucking genius of sick!
在切弗·查略斯熟睡时下毒?
Poison Chev Chelios in his sleep?
真像莎士比亚的戏剧啊
That's like some Shakespeare or some shit.
那棒把他打得够惨!
You knocked this dude out pretty good!
你真应该加入道奇队  兄弟
About to get you a spot on the Dodgers, son.
也许你不明白发生了什么
Maybe you don't understand what just happened.
我刚刚杀掉了你
I just fucking killed you.
千万不要太局促啊  你正上镜呢!
Try not to embarrass yourself because you're on 'Candid Camera'!
这就是我给你注射的东西!
This shit here I gave you! This is some...
中国产的高科技玩意儿
high-tech' sci-fi, Chinese synthetic bullshit!
我不知道玩意儿的确切成分  伙计!
I don't exactly know what's in this shit, dude!
我只知道一旦这东西
All I know is that once this shit...
跟你的血细胞结合起来
...has binded with your blood cells,
你就完蛋了  宝贝儿  相信我  现在已经结合了
you're fucked, baby, and believe me it's binded.
耶  你最多活一个小时  嘀嗒
Yeah' you got yourself about an hour' max. Tick-tock.
这可是真家伙
Yeah, baby... sexy... Oh' it's been real.
在你干掉唐·金之前
This shit's been real.
你真该考虑下后果
You should've thought twice before you whacked Don Kim.
早知今日  何必当初呢?
Experiencing a little 20/20 hindsight?
好好想想吧
I thought so.
现在  你可以舒服地去死了
Now' you have yourself a nice death.
混球!
Asshole!
你就像那个  哈?  全垒打!
You like that' huh? Home run!
"1个未接来电"
你以为你在干什么  伙计?
What do you think you're doing?
你不可以从我的车上踩过去!
You can't just walk on my car!
你他妈的以为你在干什么
What do you think you're doing' motherfucker'...
怎么可以从我的车上过去?
...walking on my car?
我是伊芙  欢迎您来电  但是我现在不在
It's Eve. I'm glad you called, but I'm not here.
如果您不是推销员的话
Leave a message,
请给我留言
unless you're selling something 'cause I'm not interested.
如果是  我不会感兴趣的  那就...  等下  时间到了
If you're not, then just... Wait, time's up.
买个手机吧  亲爱的  拜托了!
Get a cell phone' honey. Please?
快接啊
Come on.
快接  快接
迈尔斯医生办公室  能为您服务吗?
Dr' Miles office' may I help you?
嗯  请让他接电话
Yeah' let me speak to him.
对不起  医生现在不在  需要留言吗?
I'm sorry, but the doctor isn't in. May I take a message?
-他在哪里?  -我没听清  先生?
Where is he?  -I beg your pardon' sir?
他他妈的在哪里?
Where the fuck is he?
不...  耶!
No... yeah!
你是哪里人?
Where you from?
我不知道  先生  我只负责接电话
I don't know, sir. This is his answering service.
-天那  -要我帮你寻呼他吗?
Jesus fucking Christ.  -Would you like me to page him?
嗯  好的
Yeah, fine.
告诉医生  如果他一个小时内不回电
Please let the doctor know that Chev Chelios is a dead man,
-切弗·查略斯就是死人了  -能拼一下吗?
if he can't call me back within the hour.  -Could you spell that?
-嗯  D-E-A-D(死)!  查略斯  -好的  先生
Yeah' D-E-A-D! Chelios.  -Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好  -凯洛  你昨晚去哪里了?
Hello.  -Kaylo, where were you last night?
-怎么了切弗?  -我问你昨晚去哪里了?
What's up' Chev?  -I said' where were you last night?
我...
I...
-想知道昨晚发生了什么吗?  -什么?
Well, want to know what I was doing?  -What?
-我被人谋杀  蠢蛋  -什么?
Getting killed' you plum.  -What?
耶  知道你听清了  他妈的瑞奇·维罗纳...
Yeah' you heard me. Ricky fuckin' Verona...
-瑞奇·维罗纳?  -谁会想到...
Ricky Verona?  -Who'd a thought...
那个婊子在我睡觉的时候阴我?
that little bitch had the stones to wet me in my own crib?
-太不可思议了  恩  说重点  -说什么?
I mean, it's inconceivable. Yet, here we are.  -Where are we?
我都快死了  你还像个傻瓜似的
I'm dead and you're simple.
听我说的  你放出话说我在找维罗
Now listen to me. Put the word out I'm looking for Verona.
-有人看到他的话就打电话给我  明白?  -我...
Anyone sees him you call me, understand?  -I...
我在死之前一定要逮到那混蛋
I'm gonna get that little fucker if it's the last thing I do.
这可能是我临终前最后一件事了  你明白吗?
It may actually be the last thing I do.
-瑞奇·维罗纳  -照我说的做  凯洛?
You understand?  -Ricky Verona.
找到他!
You copy?  -Yeah.
"奥兰多的地盘"
Find him!
-嘿  伙计!  -你他妈想干什么?
Hey, man!
-你他妈想干什么?  带我去哪里?  -操你!
What the fuck you doing? Where am I going?  -Fuck you!
来厕所没用  你在干什么?
Bathroom don't work. What you doing?
-唷  切弗...  -维罗在哪里?
Yo, Chevy...  -Where's Verona?
-说啊!  -说什么?
Talk!  -What about?
-别耍我!  -我没有!  冷静点!
Don't fuck with me!  -I'm not! Just calm down!
别叫我冷静!
Don't tell me to calm down!
-我操啊  伙计!  -奥兰多?  你还好吗?
Fuck, man!  -Orlando? You all right?
嘿  这里有个拿着枪的白鬼
Hey, there's a white nigger with a gun up in here!
你们别乱来  贱人们
Just be still' motherfuckers!
看到了吗?  在这儿我想帮你呢  伙计
You see that? I'm trying to help you here' man.
我要找到瑞奇·维罗纳
I gotta find Ricky Verona.
-为什么我会知道维罗在哪里?  -是啊  是啊
Why would I know where Verona is?  -Yeah, yeah.
你是不知道啊  但你会告诉我的
You don't know, but you're gonna tell me.
否则我就把你脑子轰到马桶里去!
Or I'm gonna blow your brains into the fuckin' toilet!
我要杀了他!
I'm gonna fucking kill him!
啊!  放下你的枪!  这白人没有恶意的!
Whoa! Put your guns down! The white man is cool!
这白人...  这白人没有恶意的!
The white man is... The white man is cool!
你们这些索马里来的黑鬼
Y'all like them Somalia niggers.
听着  切弗来这里商量一些事情
Now look, Chevy came here to discuss something.
我们会文明地交谈的  是吧  切弗?
We gonna discuss this shit in a civilized manner. Chevy?
-你是有问题要问  还是有什么想法?  -维罗在哪里?
You had a question? Or a point to make?  -Where's Verona?
我跟瑞奇·维罗纳没任何关系的
Okay' I'm not affiliated with Ricky Verona.
安塞姆的案子是你们一起做的  别他妈的跟我胡说!
You pulled the Anselmo job together. Don't fuckin' bullshit me!
冷静!  冷静!  冷静!
Easy! Easy! Easy!
好不好?  事情已经清楚了
All right? Things are beginning to clarify.
想知道是怎么回事吗?  让我们来讲清楚
See how that works' D? Discussion leads to clarity.
我以前就告诉过你
That's what I was telling you before.
很显然  你被假象给骗了
Look' you're operating under a false pretence.
瑞奇和我并没有...
Ricky and I did not pull...
一起做安塞姆的案子
the Anselmo job together.
事实上  他在那案子上摆了我一道
Ricky fucked me on the Anselmo job.
瑞奇·维罗纳现在还差我7500美元呢
In fact, Ricky Verona still owes me $7,500.
-跟我听到的不一样  -但事实就是那样
Not how I heard it.  -But that's the way it is.
所以  你明白了吧  我不知道维罗在哪
So, you see' I don't know where Verona is. If I did,
如果我知道了  我一定会去打得他屁滚尿流的
I'd probably be there right now' beating the Gucci off his ass.
好吧
All right.
没事了
那正是我所说的  非常文明
That's what I'm talking about. That's almost civilized.
妈的  伙计  你怎么了?
Shit' dude. What's wrong with you?
我会找到瑞奇·维罗纳的
I gotta find Ricky Verona.
很明显
Well' obviously.
你今天已经把咱们的事都搞明白了
You've made that point abundantly clear to all of us here' today.
我还能怎么帮你?
How can I help you?
给我点可卡因  你有可卡因吧?
Just give me some coke. You got any coke?
现在你又想来羞辱我了?
Now you're just going to come in here and insult me?
-我知道你有可卡因  -你认为人人都会随身携带吗?
I know you got coke.  -You think every brother's carrying?
快点  我时间不多!
Come on, I don't have time!
给我点就是了
Just give me something.
-我要死在这里了  -我看得出来
I'm really dying, here.  -I can see that.
你懂不懂  我真的他妈的要死了!
No, I'm really fucking dying!
听着  如果我无法找到瑞奇·维罗纳...
Look, if I don't find Ricky Verona...
我能向你要点可卡因吗?
May I please have some coke?
-你要把可卡因当药用?  -不错
You saying this is medicinal-use coke?  -That's right.
唔?
Well?
-怎么了?  -这可不是免费的  黑鬼
What?  -This shit ain't free, nigger.
够了
That's enough.
什么  你就在这里吸?  切弗  别这样啊  伙计!
What' you gonna do the shit right here? Chevy, come on, man!
啊  上帝!
Oh' God!
切弗...
Chevy...
啊!  这他妈...
What the...
-啊  太棒了  太棒了  -很棒啊  对吧?
Oh' that's good. That's good.  -That's good' right?
那么你为什么要找维罗?
Why you looking for Verona' anyway?
中国佬雇他来杀我
Some Chinese assholes hired him to kill me.
-这跟唐·金的死有关  -你怎么知道的?
This is about Don Kim.  -What do you know about it?
-我知道是你杀的  -当然了  是我杀的
I know you pulled the trigger.  -Of course' I pulled the trigger.
我为什么不杀他?
Why wouldn't I pull the fuckin' trigger?
哇...  唷  查略斯  你还好吗?
Whoa... Yo, Chelios, you good?
-这玩意儿不起作用  -什么?
This shit ain't working.  -Excuse me?
我知道该怎么做了
I know what I have to do.
唔  妈的  男人要做他该做的事了
Well, shit. A man's got to do what a man's got to do.
-你要做什么?  -我要揍几个黑鬼
What is it you gotta do?  -I gotta kick some black ass.
什么?
What?
-妈的!  -又来了
Shit!  -There he goes again.
谁想尝尝白人的肉啊?
Who wants white meat?
别扯蛋了  蠢货!
You ain't got shit, motherfucker!
-把他妈棍子放下  婊子!  -同性恋!
Put that fuckin' twig down, bitch!  -Faggot!
快滚吧  婊子!
Get the fuck out of here, bitch!
-医生?  -还好吗  医生?
Doc?  -What's up, Doc?
-操你  你个蠢货!  -你怎么还没死?
You motherfucker!  -Why aren't you dead yet?
-你他妈在干什么?  -来找你了  混蛋
What the fuck you doing?  -Coming for you.
-相信我  -啊  随你了
Fucking believe me.  -Whatever.
我会等你的  就怕你做不到
I'll be waiting, but you won't make it.
我忘了在给你的碟上说了
You should know that I'm all about hooking up with that mystery girl,
你一死
Soon as you're underground.
我就去搞我心仪已久的你的女人
I forgot to say so on that gay James Bond tape I left.
是啊  然后你还要强奸我的祖母吗?
What' and then you're gonna rape my grandmother?
啪  啪  啪  操他妈的
Bla' bla' fuckin' bla.
你听着  要是卡雷托知道了你的勾当
You listen to me. What do you think Carlito will do...
他会怎么做呢?
...when he finds out what you did?
你们这帮人都得完蛋!
Your whole crew is history!
-司机  靠边停车!  -操!
Driver, pull over!  -Fuck!
好极了
Great.
你提到卡雷托?  卡雷托现在和我是哥们了
You talking about Carlito? Because me and Carlito, we're boys now.
我们很亲密的
We're tight.
亲密?  跟你在三年级被你哥哥操一样吗?
Tight, like when your brother fucked you in 3rd grade?
你就干过口瘾吧  我做得很漂亮  不是吗  查略斯?
That's snappy. But I did you pretty good, didn't I Chelios?
-承认吧  -你等着瞧
Admit it.  -We'll see.
靠边停车!
Pull over!
-知道最精彩的部分是什么吗?  -对不起  要挂了  拜拜
Know what the best part is?  -Sorry, must go. Bye-bye.
迈尔斯医生
Yeah.  -Doctor Miles.
操  怎么这么久才回电?  天那
Fuck! What took you so long? Jesus Christ.
对不起  切弗  我刚收到信息
Sorry' Chevy' I just got the message.
好的  别提了  听着  我要死了!
Okay. Forget it. Listen, I'm dying!
我被注射了某种中国产的毒药
I've been poisoned with some Chinese synthetic shit.
-什么?  -你要为我想想办法
What?  -You've gotta fucking do something for me.
-你有什么症状?  -我的身体正在衰弱
What are your symptoms?  -It's like I'm slowing down.
-就像如入了柏油中一样  -视力模糊吗?
Stuck in tar.  -Blurred vision?
-是啊  -头晕吗?
Yeah.  -Dizzy?
-当然了  -胸口疼吗?
Sure.  -Any pain in your chest?
不太疼  我现在感觉不错
Not really. I feel good' right now.
-你在干什么?  -开车穿过个购物中心  警察在追我
What are you doing?  -Driving through a mall' cops chasing me.
肾上腺素能让你存活
The adrenaline is what's keeping you alive.
-听不太清楚  医生  -你必须保持运动  切弗
Having a little trouble hearing you.  -You got to keep moving, Chevy.
解释一下
Explain.
如果我猜得不错  他们给你注射的是"北京鸡尾酒"
If I'm right' they gave you the Beijing cocktail.
是种非常恶性的玩意儿
It's very nasty shit.
它作用于肾上腺  阻止它与受体间的作用
It works on the adrenal gland, blocks it's receptors.
想延缓它起作用的唯一方法就是
The only thing you can do to slow it down,
保持肾上腺素的分泌
is to keep the flow of adrenaline constant.
也就是说  如果停下来  你就死了
Meaning' if you stop' you die.
别挂
Hang on.
上帝!  什么...
Jesus! What...
你还在吗?  你没事吧?
Are you there? Are you okay?
-你说什么了  医生?  -如果停下来  你就死了
What'd you say' Doc?  -If you stop, you die!
那正是我在做的  保持运动  保持血液循环
That's what I'm trying to do. Keep moving, keep the blood pumping.
切弗  你在吗?
Chevy, you there?
每当我慢下来  我的血管就像要生锈了
Every time I slow down' it's like my veins start to rust.
-你吃了什么东西吗?  -一些可卡因
Did you take anything?  -Couple grams of coke.
那只是个开始  我一个小时后到洛杉矶
That's a start. I'll be in L.A. In an hour.
一到那里我就给你打电话  保持运动!
I'll call you as soon as I get there. Do not stop moving!
的士!  唷  唷  唷!
Taxi! Yo' yo' yo!
-走!  -去哪里?
Go!  -Where we go?
开就是了!
Just drive!
-往那边走  -你想去哪里  伙计?
Would you mind...  -Where you want to go' man?
右边
Right.
-啊  该死!  -往右!
Oh' shit!  -Go right!
-嗯  好的!  -他妈的往右!
Okay! Yes!  -Go fucking right!
换个音乐
Crank the music.
声音大点!
Crank it!
不要告诉我的心  我那破碎疼痛的心
But don't tell my heart, my achy breaky heart
我想他不会明白的
I just don't think he'd understand
如果告诉了我的心  我那破碎疼痛的心
And if you tell my heart, my achy breaky heart
它就会爆裂  杀了这个人
It might blow up and kill this man
靠边停车  靠边停车
Pull over' pull over.
-谢谢  兄弟  我马上就回来  -好的  牛仔
Thanks, mate. I'll be back in one minute.  -Okay, cowboy.
嘿  伙计!
Hey' buddy!
你敢动的话就杀了你
You move' you die.
"跳跳糖"
-嘿  我是伊芙  欢迎您来电...  -操!
Hey, it's Eve. I'm glad you called...  -Fuck!
去哪里  伙计!
Where to' man?
贝弗利山庄
Beverly Hills.
"卡雷托的豪宅"
-切弗!  -嘿  老大
Chevy!  -Hey, boss.
真让我惊讶啊
What a surprise.
-发生了点紧急状况  -我也听说了
Something urgent has come up.  -So I've heard.
消息传播得就是快
Word travels fast.
-那么你都知道了?  -你真是吓倒我了  伙计
Well' then you know what happened.  -You amaze me, my friend.
我该说什么好呢?
Well, what can I say?
卡雷托  我需要你的帮助  我时间不多了
Carlito' I need your help. I don't have a lot of time.
是啊  不多了
No' not much.  -Yeah, we...
我们要找到解毒剂或其他什么玩意儿
We've gotta find an antidote, or something.
-有什么问题吗?  -他们给你注射的...
What's the matter?  -That shit they gave you...
是中国货
It's that Chinese shit.
没有解毒剂的  我也希望我可以帮上什么忙
There is no antidote. I wish there was something I could do.
-什么  就这样了?  -的确如此
What, that's it?  -Honestly,
老实说  你应该已经死了
you should be dead already.
-这真是奇迹  -奇迹?
It's a miracle.  -A miracle?
我们给马注射过那玩意儿
We give that shit to horses.
-我他妈的不相信  -我很抱歉
I don't fucking believe this.  -I'm sorry.
你别他妈的这么无情
You don't have to be so damn fucking cool about it!
-那你想要我怎么办?  -找到维罗那小人
What do you expect me to do?  -Find that punk Verona,
还有他那伙人  把他们拿去喂狼
and his whole fucking crew' and feed them to a cage of wolverines.
怎么回事?  难道你们是一伙的  还是怎么了?
What is this? What' are you boys now or something?
维罗?
Verona?
他只是个小混混而已
That's a small time punk.
-但是这次确实时机不对  -时机?
Not to say that this isn't an opportunity.  -Opportunity?
大家都知道我跟你的情谊  切弗
Everyone knows the love I have for you' Chev.
但是  这是对唐·金事件的补偿  那事情...
But maybe this makes up for the Don Kim hit which was...
-或许不太明智  -不明智?
perhaps ill-advised.  -Fuckin' Ill-advised?
香港的势力比我们想像中的要强
The heat from Hong Kong was much more than we anticipated.
唔  很显然
Well' that's outstanding' Carlito.
很高兴我的死对你还有点好处
Glad to know my death can be of some use to you.
-别那么不近人情  -我不是不近人情
Don't be difficult.  -I'm not being difficult.
不知你是否注意到了
I don't know if you noticed,
但我正要度过艰难的一天  兄弟!
but I'm having a difficult fucking day' brother!
你这是在轻视我吗?
Are you disrespecting me?
难道这不是你干的好事吗?
Is that what you're doing?
忘了这件事吧  我走了
Forget it. I'm out of here.
身子湿的不准进我的车
You're not getting in my cab' wet!
我刚刚给了你200美元  只让你等了3分钟
I just gave you $200 to wait for 3 minutes.
不准进我的车  没门!
You're not getting in my car' no way!
嗯  不错  我就要进你的车
Yeah' you're right.
基地分子!  基地分子!
Al-Qaeda! Al-Qaeda!
我爱美国!  我爱布什!
I love America! I love Bush!
我给布什投了票的!
I Voted Bush!
嘿  切弗  我的飞机晚点了
Yeah.  -Hey' Chev. My flight's delayed.
-见鬼!  -没事的  放松点
Shit!  -It's all right. Relax.
我是说  不能放松
I mean' don't relax.
他们给你注射的东西会阻止肾上腺素
That shit they gave you is cutting off your adrenaline.
兴奋  恐惧  危险
Excitement, fear, danger.
能让你的身体分泌叫做麻黄碱的化学物
It causes your body to make a chemical called ephedrine.
-他们在你体内注射了抑制剂  -操!
They introduced an inhibitor to your system.  -Fuck!
伙计  你必须要提高你体内麻黄碱的含量
You've got to massively increase the ephedrine level in your body,
以此来抵消抑制剂的作用  去医院吧
to force out the inhibitors. Go to a hospital.
找些艾福林(人造肾上腺素)
Get epinephrine' an artificial adrenaline.
一注射器有10毫克
It comes in 10-milligram syringes.
药力很强劲  注射五分之一就够了  千万别过量
A 5th of an injection will do. It's potent, so don't overdo it.
切弗?  你听到了吗?
Chevy? Did you get that?
-你听到了吗?  -嗯  Epi什么的
Did you get that?  -Yeah, epi-something.
好的  好的  我要挂了
Okay' okay. I've gotta go.
我到了再给你打电话
Now, I'll call you when I get there.
-嗯?  -切弗
Yeah?  -Chev.
嗯?
Yeah?
-切弗?  -怎么了?
Chev?  -What?
喂?
Hello?
快啊!
Come on!
操!
Mother!
-切弗?  -是的  操?
Chev?  -Yes' fuck?
我刚看见维罗的哥哥走进了王子餐馆
I just saw Verona's brother walk into the Prince.
-王子餐馆  -是的
The Prince.  -Yeah.
两分钟前  我想到这里买玉米卷  看见他进去了
I was just down here getting a taco' and he walked in' 2 minutes ago.
-那你现在在哪?  -在街对面  买玉米卷啊
Where are you' now?  -Across the street, getting a taco.
-你呢?  -我就在  在凯特琳娜街7号碰头
Where are you?  -I'm there. Meet me on 7th and Catalina.
他现在还在里面吗?
Is he in there, now?
有人跟他一起进去吗?
Did anyone go in with him?
好的  在这里等着
Right' wait here.
感觉怎么样啊  恶棍?
How'd you like that one' tough guy?
你不是很强么  啊?
How frickin' awesome was that' huh?
唔  唔  唔
Well, well.
不想说点什么吗?  你那混蛋弟弟呢?
You feel like talking? Where's your fuckin' brother?
正把你妈当妓女操呢  你个婊子!
Doing your mother like a whore, you bitch!
好极了  我想我该把你切成多少块呢?
Nice. I wonder how many steaks I could carve out of you.
你死定了  贱人!
You died' motherfucker!
是啊  想操我吗  哈?
Yeah' wanna fuck with me' ese?
什么  你的面棍也许很合适啊?
What, you rolling pin mighty good?
你他妈的以为你在干什么  哈?
What the hell you think you doing, huh?
什么  想跟我跳舞吗  贱人?
What, you want to dance with me' motherfucker?
我要操死你!  来吧!
I'll fuck you up! Come on!
上帝!  做什么都不容易啊
Jesus! Nothing's easy.
想拿着手吗?
Wanna hold hands?
-嘿  说吧  哥哥  -嘿  瑞奇
Hey, talk to me' bro.  -Hey, Ricky.
想不想给我吹箫吗?
You in the mood for sucking me off?
要么让我舔舔你的屁股啊?
Maybe let me lick your ass or something?
你是谁?  妈的!  查略斯?
Who is this? Shit! Chelios?
-你他妈的是查略斯?  -答对了  伙计
Is this fucking Chelios?  -That's right, bro.
想知道我怎么拿到你哥哥的手机的吗?
Guess how I got your brother's phone.
我想你应该全明白了
I'm sure you have it all figured out.
看来在你有机会的时候  你就应该就结果了我
Looks like you should've cut me up when you had the chance.
我听不见你说话啊
I'm having a little trouble hearing you.
你早知今日  何必当初呢?
You experiencing a little 20/20 hindsight?
你他妈应该已经死了的!
You're supposed to be fucking dead!
我有点对你注射的玩意儿上瘾了
You know, I kind of like that shit you put in me.
再给我来点  好吗?
Gonna give me some more?
-唔  我要...  我要...  -明白  明白  嘿...
Well' I'm... I'm...  -I know, I know. Hey...
这是什么?
What's this?
一条项链!  你们俩确实是同性恋  是吗?
A necklace! You guys really are faggots, aren't you?
你个贱人!
You motherfucker!
那是我爷爷传给我爸爸  然后又...
My grandfather gave that medallion to my father and then he...
操!
Fuck!
-操你!  拿那东西堵上你的屁眼吧!  -不用了  谢谢
Fuck you, man! Shove that thing up your ass!  -No thanks.
你知道  我会把它戴起来的
You know' I believe I'll hang on to it.
你也就不得不来找我了
You'll have to come find me' after all.
-是你他妈的连累死了你哥哥  -你...
Fucked up that you killed your own brother.  -You...
那玩意儿叫什么的?  Epi...  10毫克?
What's that shit? Epi... 10 milligrams?
干得漂亮  凯洛
Good work, Kaylo.
信医生请到产房
Doctor Sing to the labor room.
-混蛋!  -别挤啊!
Asshole!  -No need to push.
我在找种E开头的药
I'm looking for something that starts with "E".
英国?
England?
有意思  不  是某种人造的肾上腺素
Very funny. No. Some kind of artificial adrenaline.
-人造的肾上腺素?  -是啊  我心脏有问题?
Artificial adrenaline?  -Yeah, I've got heart problems.
-艾福林  -是的  艾福林
Epinephrine.  -Yes! Epinephrine.
我爱死你了  艾福林
I love you. Epinephrine.
我不能给你艾福林
I can't give you epinephrine.  -Why?
-为什么?  -请稍等
Just a minute.
喂!  你这是什么意思...
Oi! What do you mean...
-这是怎么回事?  -鼻速通
What is this shit?  -Nasal spray.
-可怜的婊子!  -说什么?
Miserable bitch! What?
鼻速通  那里面有艾福林成分
Nasal spray. It's got epinephrine in it.
那也能让你嗨起来的  伙计
It'll get you tweaked, man.
嘿!
Hey!
-确定是那家伙吗?  -是的
Sure that's the guy?  -Yeah.
不在这屋里
This room's clear.
哪位会说韩语的请到急诊室来?
Could anyone speaking Korean please come to ER?
有谁会说韩语...
Anyone speaking Korean...
唷  唷  唷!
Yo, yo, yo!
唷!
Yo!
站住!
Stop!
打飞机啊你!
Jerk-off!
借过!
Coming through!
我就知道你们这些贱人有艾福林
I know you motherfuckers have epinephrine.
-清理走廊!  -拐弯  手术室准备好了吗?
Clear the hallway!  -Corner. Is the OR ready?
我今天很不爽   告诉我  你这里有艾福林吧?
I'm having a bad day. Tell me you've got epinephrine on this cart!
你没事吧?
You all right?
我说告诉我艾福林在哪里!
Tell me you've got epinephrine!
-贱人!  -我不知道  我给你找找
Motherfucker!  -I don't know. I'll check.
-退后!  -别紧张!
Get back!  -Take it easy!
你他妈的懂不懂英语?
Do you understand fucking English?
懂  我只是不知道那东西在哪里面
Yes' I just don't know which draw it's in.
快点  快找!
Look!
把他妈的艾福林给我!
Give me the fucking epinephrine!
我不知道在哪里面  伙计!
I don't know where it is' man!
-这是什么地方  休息室?  -你在干什么?
What is this, a rest home?  -What are you doing back there?
快点!
Hurry up!
-退后!  -没有保险我们不能治疗
Get back!  -We can't treat without insurance.
我不知道这里有没有  给我点时间
I don't know if I have it. Give me a second!
把武器放下!
Put the weapon down!
真他妈的!  他妈的在哪里?
What the fuck! Where the fuck is it?
-我的心脏!  -什么?
My heart!  -What?
-我的心脏!  -好的  好的
My heart!  -Yeah, yeah.
快放下武器!
Drop your weapon' now!
-你以为你在做什么?  这里是医院  -闭嘴!  你!
What do you think you're doing? This is...  -Shut up! You!
找到艾福林了?
Gimme the epinephrine?
别乱来!
Don't even think about it!
Albuterol...  Flortab...  艾福林(均为药物名称)!
Albuterol... Flortab... Epinephrine!
在这里  我找到了!
Here it is! I've got it!
-拿去吧  -给我拿来
Here you go.  -Gimme that.
-混蛋  -下次我就不客气了啊
Asshole.  -I'm not gonna tell you again.
...还好吗?  安静下来
...all right? Just be quiet.
电我
Juice me.
电击?
Juice?
做就是了
Do it.
-好的  -快点!
All right.  -Come on!
我可没时间等你一天啊
I haven't got all day.
好的  我要那两个东西...  把它们给我
Okay, I need both of them to... Give them to me.
一
One.
二  开始!
Two. Clear!
他妈的退后!
Get the fuck back!
出去!
Get out!
他说这玩意儿要打多少的?
How much of this stuff did he say to take?
切弗  我在飞机上了  伙计
Chevy, we're in the air, man.
-你拿到药了吗?  -拿到了
Did you get the stuff?  -Got it.
-打了吗?  -嗯
Did you take it?  -Yup.
-你不是都打下去了吧?  -嗯
You took the whole thing.  -Yup.
-我说五分之一  那玩意儿会杀了你的  -对啊
I said one 5th. The shit's gonna kill you.  -Right.
-胸口像着火了?  -对头
Chest on fire?  -Check.
-但是你感觉很冷  -对头
But you're cold.  -Check.
-你下面勃起了吧  是吗?  -让我看看
And you've got a steel hard on, don't you?  -Let me check.
-对头  -你的血管受到了刺激
Check.  -Your blood vessels are stimulated.
尿道括约肌因此也被绷紧  你要被尿给憋死了
Urinary sphincter's so tight' you couldn't piss to save your life.
尿道括约肌  对头!
Urinary sphincter' check!
去搞点唯寇锭  你还在医院吧?(止痛药  滥用可上瘾)
Get some Vicodin. You at the hospital?
不在了
Negative.
去搞点大麻  如果不在30分钟内...
Get some grass. That shit'll be out of your system...
...把那玩意儿排出体内的话  你就玩完了
...in 30 minutes, or it'll kill you.
飞机上话费很贵
This is costing me a fortune.
20分钟后着陆了再给你打电话
I'll call you in 20 minutes when we land.
-明白  -嘿  切弗?
Copy.  -Hey, Chevy?
你是个好人  我很了解你
You're a good dude. Been nice knowing you.
明白  挂了
Copy, out.
急诊而已
Some medical emergency.
一名男子造成全市性的大混乱
Police have declined to name...
已有1人死亡  数十人受伤
...the man they say is still at large,
并有数千美元的财产损失
on a citywide rampage that has left one man dead,
警方拒绝透露该男子姓名
dozens injured,
目前  该男子依然逍遥法外
and hundreds of thousands of dollars of damage...
嫌疑犯嗜杀成性  是名职业杀手
in it's smoking, bloody wake. The suspect is a professional killer...
曾参与组织犯罪  警方也有其大量犯罪记录
with ties to organized crime and a long police record.
他持有枪械  高度危险
He is considered armed and highly dangerous.
我们会对此事件进行跟踪报道
We now continue with regularly scheduled programming,
直至案件侦破
but stay tuned for continuing coverage of this bizarre story,
下面正常播出节目
as it unfolds.
你所说的橄榄  洋葱  柠檬  莱檬...
What your saying is that next to olives, onions, lemons and limes...
-啊  见鬼!  -别乱来!
Oh' shit! Take it easy.
退后  猪!
Get back, pig!
我...  只是把...
I... just give me the...
那你来啊  跑给我看看  小猪
Come on, then. Let's see you run, piggy.
来啊  小猪
Come on' piggy.
把枪给我  我们可以谈谈的
Give me the gun. Let's talk this over.
是啊  你想要吗?  那边
Yeah' you want it? There.
-我们走  快啊  -小心点
Honey, let's go. Come on.  -Be careful.
好的  我去找人来帮忙  好吗?
All right. I'm gonna get some help' all right?
嗯
Yeah.
-嘿  你给我打过电话的啊?  -你整天都在家里的吗?
Hey, did you try to call?  -You've been home all day?
-我睡得太熟了  -熟睡  很好  伊芙
I was sleeping in.  -Sleeping in. That's great' Eve.
好极了
Super great.
你现在休息够了吧?  很高兴听到你这样说
You all rested, now? Glad to hear it.
听着  我被人下了致命的毒
Listen' I've been fatally poisoned.
马上会有个变态来折磨死你
A psychopath's on his way over to torture and kill you,
你不要出去  我马上就过来
but don't get out of bed' I'll be over in a flash.
给我烤点饼干吧?
Could you fry up a waffle?
当然了  来吧  我在这儿等你
Sure, yeah. Come on over. I'll be here.
好的  别乱走  好了
Right, you'll be there. Okay.
再见
Bye.
那么  我们去抓那个婊子!
So, let's go get the bitch!
"伊芙的公寓"
恨死你了
I hate you.
等一下
Second.
快啊
Come on!
快啊  拜托!
Come on, please!
来了  来了  老天!
All right' all right. Jesus!
啊  我的天!
Oh my God!
-这难道是你的新造型吗?  -是啊  你喜欢吗?
Is this your new look or something?  -Yeah, you into it?
别恶心我了
It's gross.
你在找我其他的男朋友吗?
Are you looking for my other boyfriend?
啊  太棒了!
Yes!
-你今天没有看电视吧  是吗?  -没有  怎么了?
You haven't watched TV today' right?  -No' why?
那就别想了  来吧  我们走
Didn't think so. Come on, we're leaving.
你说什么呢?  别这么怪异
Don't be a freak.
穿上衣服
Get dressed.
你能调一下微波炉的时间吗?
Actually, can you change the clock on the microwave?
我调不回去了
I never changed it back.
-什么?  -那微波炉
What?  -The microwave.
你能调一下微波炉的时间吗?
Change the clock. The daylight savings time,
换成夏令时之后我调不回去了
I never changed it back.
-那微波炉?  -是的
The microwave?  -Yes.
听着  我本来买了些花  在路上被搞坏了
Listen' I bought you some flowers. They got fucked up on the way over.
对我真好!  你没事吧?
That's sweet! You okay?
你看上去就像磕了药一样
You look like you're on drugs or something.
你是爱我的  对吗?
You love me' yeah?
嗯
Yes.
-那我需要你为我做点事情  -什么事  发生什么了?
Then I need you to do something for me.  -What? What's wrong?
我要你现在就穿上衣服跟我走
I need you to put some clothes on and come with me, right now.
-不  -我会去把微波炉的时间调好的
No.  -I'll change the clock on the microwave.
好的  好吧
Okay. All right.
药效消失了
Shit's wearing off.
-饼干炉还开着  想吃的话自己做  -好极了
The waffle iron's on if you want to make one.  -Great.
好极了
Great.
感觉你怎么这么紧张  想吸点大麻吗?
You're so stressed out. Want some pot?
好的!  不!
Yeah! No!
-准备好了  怎么了?  -我把手给烫伤了
Ready! What's wrong?  -I burned my hand.
-啊  上帝  让我看看!  -我们走吧  别担心  嘿!
Oh, my God! Let me see it!  -Don't worry about it. Hey!
这他妈...
What the...
-对不起  -你不必这样子的
I'm sorry.  -That was completely uncalled for.
我们可不可以...
Can we just...
好的
Fine.
车停在后面
Parked out the back.  -Oh.
-亲爱的!  那东西...  -什么东西
Darn! That... thing.  -What thing?
饼干机  我要去把它关了
The waffle thing. I gotta turn it off.
喂?
Hello?
好的  太有趣了
All right, very funny.
天哪  真讨嫌
God' I hate that.
你是想把这房子给烧了吗?
Do you want to burn the building down?
-哎哟!  -对不起  亲爱的
Ouch!  -Sorry, honey.
真糟糕  切弗
Nice one. Chev?
啊  我的万金油
Oh, there's my Tiger Balm.
对天发誓  切弗
I swear to God' Chev.
我不知道你在找什么  但是这对你没用的
I don't know what you're on, but it isn't working for you.
我的护手霜!  你是在找这个吧
My hand cream! That's where you went.
切弗  来帮帮我啊?
Chev? Can I have some help, here?
-你的车在哪里?  -实际上  我是搭的计程车
Where's your car?  -Actually, I took a cab.
"唐人街"
真让我难堪
You're embarrassing me.
我没有时间去挑这个
I didn't have a lot of time to pick this out.
那么为什么我们要到这儿来
So' why are we here?
事情不是...  事情不是这么简单的  就像人常说的
This isn't gonna be... This isn't gonna be easy' as they say.
啊  操啊
Oh, fucker.
-没事了  现在好了  -对不起
All right' here it is.  -Sorry.
-我告诉过你我曾是个电玩制作人  -是啊?
I told you I was a video game programmer.  -Yeah?
我是说谎的
That was a lie.
实际上...
Actually...
我杀人的
I kill people.
我是名自由职业杀手
Professional hitman.
是西海岸犯罪集团的骨干分子
I freelance for a major West Coast crime syndicate.
昨晚的活没什么特别
Last night was a job like 100 others.
拿人钱财替人消灾
High dollar hit' nothing special.
香港的三合会
The Triads, from Hong Kong,
意图染指当地地下毒品交易
had been moving in on the local drug cartels.
我的目标是他们在洛杉矶的头号人物
My target was the number 1 man in Los Angeles, Don Kim.
那么?
Well?
你在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
那时  一个愚蠢的念头涌入了我的脑海
Then, this insane idea comes through the back of my head,
就跟近距离被4.5毫米子弹射中了一样
like a.45 slug at close range.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
-我赢得了什么吗?  -你的命  蠢货
Did I win something?  -Your life, jackass.
你的头值10万美元呢  迟早会有人来杀你的
100 grand wants you dead. So' sooner or later it's gonna happen'
但是不会是我
but I'm not doing it.
我明白了
I see.
与其给我点报酬
Instead you're gonna do something for me.
你还不如离开这城市  消失掉
You're gonna get out of town. Disappear.
我不管你去哪里  或者做什么
I don't care where you go or what you do'
我只要求你能消失48小时
so long as you're invisible for 48 hours. That's all I ask.
48小时?
48 hours?
或者  如果你愿意  我们也可以换个方式
Or, if you prefer, we can do it the other way.
我完成我的任务  你上西天见菩萨
The way where I go to work' and you meet Buddha.
明白了吗?  我放弃了
You see? I quit.
我为你放弃了买卖
I quit the business' for you.
-为我?  -是啊
For me?  -Yeah.
我本打算昨晚给你打电话告诉你一切
I figure I call you that night and tell you everything.
我们上飞机离开这鬼地方  再也不回来
We get on a plane' leave this shit' never come back.
-很疯狂吧  哈?  -你真是太怪异了
Pretty crazy, huh?  -You are so weird.
-那我们要去旅行吗?  -唔...
Are we going on a trip?  -Well...
我可能要去  但是你不会跟着我...
I might be going on a trip, but you're not coming with me...
-拜托!  等等!  拜托!  -杀手  切弗?
Please! Wait' please!  -Mob hits, Chev?
中国的毒药?  你知道你有多可笑吗?
Chinese poison? Do you know how ridiculous you sound?
如果你想跟我分手  至少应该说实话!
If you're leaving me' then tell me the truth!
好吧  你觉得这听起来很疯狂
Oh' right. You think it sounds crazy.
你觉得我什么感觉?  我不得不过这种狗屁日子
How do you think I feel? I have to live this shit!
切弗?  切弗?
Chev? Chev?
你怎么了?
What's wrong?
-等等  你相信我吗?  -不
Wait a minute' you trust me?  -No.
-跟我做爱  -什么?
Make love to me.  -What?
-我想这会有作用的  -什么?  你没开玩笑吧?  不许碰我!
I think it'll help.  -What? Are you kidding? Get off me!
-脱掉你的衣服  -不!
Take your clothes off.  -No!
不!
No!
-你不是说想要自然些吗?  -你疯了吧!
You said you wanted to be more spontaneous.  -You're crazy!
你就是个精虫上脑的行尸走肉
You're an adrenaline junkie with no soul!
-救救我  伊芙  救救我的命  -住手!
Save me, Eve. Save my life!  -Stop it!
对不起  我的天  你还好吗?
I'm sorry. Oh my God' are you okay?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
不!  不!
No! No!
该死!
Shit!
起来!
Get off!
你这禽兽!
You filthy animal!
就在这里  在大家面前上我吧!
Take me right here' in front of everyone!
就这样!
That's it!
快  做啊!
Come on! Do it!
-你在等什么?  -上帝!
What are you waiting for?  -Jesus!
-快啊!  -我在努力呢!  嘘!
Come on!  -I'm trying!
啊  天呢  现在你不能勃起了?
Oh' God! Now you can't get it up?
-快啊  快起来!  -我已经起来了!
Come on' get it up!  -I'll fucking get it up!
-该死的  切弗!  -闭嘴!
Goddamnit, Chev!  -Shut up!
我还活着!  我还活着!
I'm alive! I'm alive!
我还活着!  你们这些贱人!
I'm alive, you motherfuckers!
啊  我的天!  哇!
Oh' my God! Wow!
啊  我的天!  太棒了!
Oh, my God! Yes!
-喂  -你干什么?
Yeah?  -What are you doing?
-喂  -我找到了维罗
I've got Verona.  -Kaylo?
-凯洛?  -我找到了维罗  伙计!
I've got Verona, man.
-什么?  -真的?
What?  -No shit?
-你在哪里?  -唐·金服装厂的楼上
Where are you?  -Don Kim's shirt factory, upstairs.
-你有毛病啊?  -阿拉米达街5号?
What's the matter with you?  -5th and Alameda?
-阿拉米达街5号?  -别让那混蛋离开你的视线!
Who's at 5th and Alameda?  -Don't let that fucker out of your sight!
-听到了吗?  我10分钟后到  明白?  -好的  切弗
Hear me? With you in 10 minutes. You got it?  -Yeah' Chev.
亲爱的  我要走了  希望你理解
Honey, I gotta go. Please understand.
不  切弗  我搞不懂
No, Chev, I do not understand!
哦  宝贝
Oh, baby!
我会给你打电话的!
I'll call you!
啊  上帝  你们在看什么?
What are you looking at?
嘿  伙计  你怎么了?  你是瘾君子?
Hey man' what's the matter with you? You a crackhead?
是啊  你快点  好吗?
Right' just step on it' all right?
你不会死在我车上的  瘾君子
You're won't die in my cab, crackhead.
我给你点好东西
I got something for you.
来点海地货
Take this Haitian shit.
原汁原味  纯天然的
This shit is some hardcore shit. It's made from plant shit.
嘿  你笑什么?  看这里  看见没有?
Hey, what are you laughing at? Look at this. You see that?
真正的男人应该像我这样  瘾君子  这就是力量
That's what a man look like, crackhead. That's power.
再看看你
Now look at you.
什么玩意儿
What the hell.
不错吧?
Yeah.
难吃死了
It tastes like ass.
那就对了  恶棍  等会儿就知道了
That's right' devil. You wait.
-他妈的闭嘴!  -不要!
Shut the fuck up!  -No!
-不要!  -他妈的闭嘴!
No!  -Shut the fuck up!
哇  死了!  操他!
Whoop, there it is! Fuck him!
"唐·金的服装厂"
我们到了
We're here.
-你刚才说这里面有什么?  -跟你说了  原汁原味的
What'd you say was in this stuff?  -I told you' it's hardcore.
一共5.55美元
It'll be $5.55.
-都给你了  伙计  -祝你今天愉快  恶棍
It's all you, man.  -Have a nice day, devil.
糟透了
This is fucked.
嘿  他要去哪里?
Where's he going?
嗯  好的  你打电话给我干什么  就是说这破事?
Yeah' okay. How the fuck you going to call me' talking shit?
我他妈一巴掌拍死你  我不知道他...
I'm gonna smack the hell out of you. I don't know where he at...
他妈的没事找事!
Fucking call me talking shit!
我有我的工作  我正做自己的事情呢
I'm doing my job. I'm doing my shit.
我正常得很  做自己该做的事  我他妈的是屋顶...
I'm out here, doing what I do. I'm a rooftop mother...
嘿!  切弗!  怎么了  家伙?
Hey, Chevy! What's up' dog?
一切都好吗?  你好吗?
Everything okay? You chillin'? You good?
-真他妈的碰巧啊!  -你说什么呢  伙计?
What a coincidence!  -What do you mean?
你在干什么  等公交车?
What, you waiting for a bus?
不  实际上  也许是直升机吧
Actually' I thought a helicopter...
-这他妈的怎么回事?  -什么?
What is this?  -What?
-你给中国人工作?  -中国人?
You working for the Chinese?  -The Chinese?
-别这样伙计  你疯了?  我不会背叛你的
You crazy? I wouldn't do that to you.
我是疯了  凯洛在哪里?
I am crazy. Where's Kaylo?
-好的  "叮"  时间到了  -"叮"是什么意思?
Okay' ding. Time's up.  -What do you mean' "ding"?
"叮"是什么意思?
What do you mean, "ding"?
那狗娘养的在哪里?
Where is that motherfucker?
切弗
Chev.
-这他妈的是什么?  -切弗  宝贝儿  别乱来
What the fuck is this?  -Chev, baby. Take it easy.
啊  你是指这样吗?
Oh' you mean like this?
快告诉我维罗那个小杂碎在哪里
Now you tell me where that little toe-rag motherfucker is. Verona.
维罗跟这没有任何关系
Verona's got nothing to do with this.
什么?
What?
-唐·卡洛斯想要你在街上消失  -卡雷托?
Don Carlos wants you off the streets.  -Carlito?
你已经完全失去理智了  伙计
You've totally lost your shit, dog.
你上电视了  破坏财产  违法乱纪
You're all over TV. Destroying property, making unauthorized hits...
你让整个社团的处境很尴尬
You're causing the organization a great deal of embarrassment.
-你告诉我是卡雷托吩咐你们做的?  -听着
You're telling me Carlito wanted this?  -Look'
别担心  我们会收拾维罗的
don't worry' we'll take care of Verona.
你最好去找个美妙
The best thing for you to do is find some nice'
黑暗  安静的角落
dark' quiet place and...
等死
just die.
等死  我的前额上写着"讨厌鬼"几个字吗?
Just die. You think I've got "cunt" written on my forehead?
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
-我们终究会死的  对吧?  -嗯
We all got to die sometime, right?  -Yeah.
我们终究会死的
We all got to die sometime.
那么  我就去死吧
So' I'll just die.
这他妈...
What the...
-这他妈...  -你中弹了!
Of all the fuckin'...  -You got shot!
狗娘...
Mother...
-上帝!  -伊芙  让开!
Jesus! Eve, move!
-你个混蛋!  -别那样跟他说话!
You' asshole!  -Don't talk to him like that!
-我男朋友会杀人的!  -很好!
My boyfriend kills people!  -Nice.
啊  天那!
Oh' God!
我得看看你是不是说的实话
I had to see if you were telling the truth.
过来
Come on.
不  等一下!
No, wait!
现在过来吧
Now, come on.
啊  天那!
Oh' God!
啊  真该死!
Oh, dammit!
-我忘记吃避孕药了!  -什么?
I forgot to take my birth control pills.  -What?
-钥匙在哪里?  钥匙!  -这里
Where are the keys? The keys!  -Here.
-过来!  过来!  -我的东西!
Come! Come!  -My stuff!
我那些东西!
All my stuff!
-你没有说谎!  -欢迎加入我的生活!
You weren't lying!  -Welcome to my life.
不  我是指你为我放弃了这一切
No, I mean... that you would give it all up for me.
是啊
Yeah.
-还有那些呢?  -毒药的事情也是真的
And the other part?  -The poison's true' too.
那...  那就是说...
Then... that means...
非常对  伊芙
Pretty much, Eve.
-那我们该怎么办呢?  -只有肾上腺素才能延缓发作
How can we stop it?  -Only adrenaline can slow it down.
-那么  当我们在唐人街的时候...?  -是的  对不起
So, when we were in Chinatown?  -Yeah. Sorry.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
-让你多活一会儿啊  -什么?
This'll get you going.  -What?
-来吧  我们接着刚才继续做  -啊  老天
Come on, let's finish what you started.  -Oh, boy.
啊  就这样  这对我很有效
Oh, that's it. That's really working for me.
-你喜欢这样吗?  -趴着别动!
You like that?  -Stay down!
狗娘养的!
Motherfuck!
上帝!  啊  就是这样  宝贝儿  继续
Jesus! Yeah, that's it' baby. Just a little more.
趴着别动  伊芙
Stay down, Eve.
-上帝!  -啊  你的真大!
Jesus.  -Oh, you're so big!
啊  我的上帝!
Oh my God!
再多来几下...
Just a touch...
-怎么回事?  -跟往常一样  舒服完了就睡觉?
What's that matter?  -So you can fall asleep like always?
想得倒美
I don't think so.
老天!  操!
Jesus! Fuck!
他们真的...
Are they really...
他们死了
They're dead.
你怎么...  怎么能那么做?
How do you... How can you do that?
我告诉过你  但我已经退出了
I told you, baby. I quit.
-你要去哪?  -呆在这里  亲爱的
Where are you going?  -Stay there, honey.
-上帝!  操!  -切弗!
Jesus! Fuck!  -Chev!
混蛋
Asshole!
我的腿没有知觉了
I can't feel my leg.
该死!  我给你打了半小时的电话
Shit! I've been trying to call you for a half hour.
-你他妈的在哪里?  -在我办公室
Where the fuck have you been?  -In my office.
-你能过来吗?  -当然了
Can you make it over here?  -Sure' why not?
巧克力?
Chocolate'
这个金色食品市场的254美元的收据怎么回事?
what's this fucking receipt from Gold Foods Market for $254?
快餐
Snacks.
我讨厌电视
I hate television.
我又欠你人情了  医生
I owe you again, Doc.
切弗  你是我最好的顾客
Chevy' you're my best customer.
-这是什么东西?  -合成的肾上腺素...
What is this stuff?  -Synthetic epinephrine...
-搭配在盐水里面  -感觉有点兴奋啊
diluted with some saline.  -Feels sort of good.
唔  我还在里面加了些兴奋剂
Well, I got a little meth in there' too.
是那些内啡肽起的作用(激素群  可缓解痛感并影响情绪)
You're feeling the endorphins.
等等  我没有好起来吗?
Wait a minute. I'm not better?
是啊  你没有好起来
No' you're not better.
你的病情很严峻  你还能活着
You're in such shit shape' it's stunning.
已经让我感到很吃惊了
I can't believe your heart's beating.
真应该把你写进医药杂志里面去
You should be in a fucking medical journal.
那么你打算怎么办?
So, what are you going to do?
方案是给你注射抗化剂
The solution acts as a competing inhibitor.
这能将毒药排出你的受体
It's pushing the poison out of your receptors'
并用另外一种的化学物质来代替  这只是暂时性的方案
and replacing it with a chemical. It's just a temporary fix.
那接着呢?
Then what?
接着你就完蛋了
Then you're fucked.
我可以给你接上生命维系系统  让你多活几天
I can put you on life support and string this out for a few days.
但你迟早会进入休克的状态的
But you're going to go into a comma at some point.
她知道吗?
Does she know?
不如你注射点东西吧?
Why don't I load you up with something,
那样你就可以在美梦中死去
and you can go out in a beautiful dream.
美梦
A dream.
要我那样做吗?
Can I do that for you?
不  不  不  那不是我想要的
No, no, no. That's not what I want.
那你想要什么?
What do you want?
一小时
One hour.
我需要一个小时
I want one hour.
他在那里跟她做爱  就在售报机边
Give me a fuckin' break.
从洛杉矶早上9点开始的大破坏依然继续
So, the wild rampage that began 9am in L.A. Continues.
犯罪嫌疑人也依然逍遥法外
The suspect, still at large.
我们没有给他注射足量的毒药
We didn't give him enough of the Chinese shit.
是那样吗?
You think?
伙计  是他!
Dude, it's him!
-还好吗  死人?  -早上好  低能儿
What's up' corpse?  -Bonjour, douche bag,
我有笔你会感兴趣的交易
Thought you might be interested in a deal.
啊  你现在成商人了?
Oh, you a dealer, now?
别管我是什么
Don't you worry about what I am.
-听着  我需要解毒剂  -啊  解毒剂?
Listen, I want the antidote.  -Oh, the antidote?
-不错  解毒剂  -那你打算给我什么  混蛋?
That's right, the antidote.  -What you prepared to give me?
从你哥哥那里拿来的那串项链
How about the jewelry I got off that faggot brother of yours'...
怎么样啊  同性恋?
...you cocksucker?
-可别上火啊  你个小鸡巴  -好吧
Don't pop a blood vessel, you little penis.  -Okay.
-同意交易了?  -随你!
You like the deal?  -Whatever!
20分钟后在林特酒店见面
Be at the downtown Lint in 20 minutes.
-你知道地方吧?  -嗯  我知道
You know the spot?  -Yeah.
别迟到啊  否则我就拿这东西换妓女给我手淫去了
Don't be late, or I'll trade the thing to a whore for a hand job.
听着  我说了我会...  会到的  操!
Look' I said I said I'd fuckin' be... Fuck!
再见了  阳光男孩
See you later, sunshine. ...turn that shit off.
真他妈的  操!
Dammit! Fuck!
唷  我是维罗  你肯定不会相信我刚刚接到了谁的电话
Yo' it's Verona. You won't believe this call I just got.
没事的  宝贝儿
It's gonna be all right, baby.
-但是你说了...  -不  不会的
But you said...  -No, no.
形势不同了
Things have changed.
他那里有解药  我可以跟他做交易
There's an antidote. I can make a deal for it,
但是我必须一个人去
but I got to go alone.
-我很害怕  -没事的
I'm scared.  -Of course.
现在你很安全  我会回来的
You'll be safe, now. And I'll be back.
保证!
Promise?
我保证
I promise.
怎么了  兄弟?
What's happening' bro?
-我做错什么了?  -你刚刚说什么?
Where did I go wrong?  -You fuckin' just say something?
真是对牛弹琴
It's like talking to the wall.
-妈妈?  -我很吃惊你还记得你有个妈妈
Mom?  -I'm amazed you remember you have a mother.
你既不给我打电话  也不写信
You never call, you never write.
自从你16岁跑出家门我就没再见过你
I haven't seen you since you ran out at 16.
耶  耶  对  妈妈  你倒出来的安定药片噼里啪啦的
Yeah, yeah. Right' Mom. With you popping Valium like tic tacs'
每两周上一个王八蛋
boning a new asshole every 2 weeks,
我为什么还要忍受这个?
why wouldn't I stick around with fun like that?
-拜托  我可空说这个  -你没有时间了  没有了
Please' I haven't got time for this.  -You got no time, period.
-奥兰多?  -你这固执的狗娘养的家伙    查略斯
Orlando?  -You're a persistent motherfucker, Chelios.
-我给了你这些  -这太奇怪了
I give you that.  -This is weird.
我知道很奇怪  但这总是要结束的
I know this is weird, but this has got to stop sometimes...
你以为你是谁?
What do you think you are,
麦克尔·麦尔斯?(《月光光心慌慌》中杀人狂的名字)
Michael Myers?
我很佩服你  他们对你采取了行动  你还在垂死挣扎?
They pop you and you keep getting up?
-我是终结者  -你曾经是  但是我们有了新的选择
I'm the terminator.  -You was, but here's a new gun in town.
你知道我不会接受的
You know, I just don't get it.
当你有机会的时候为什么没杀掉我?
Why didn't you just cut me up when you had the chance?
那太简单了  狗娘养的  看看你
Too easy, motherfucker. Look at you.
双重性格  施虐受虐狂倾向...
Bi-polar, sadomasochistic tendencies...
瘾君子  暴力狂...
Adrenaline junkie, addicted to violence...
很可能每天都在寻找强烈的快感
Probably spends every day of his life looking for the big rush.
折磨人
Carving up a guy,
看他在自己的血泊和污秽中尖叫
while he screams in his own blood and excrement, would be like...
就像是你的本能  勇士之死
like a gift. A warriors death.
该死  你大概很享受那种感觉吧?
Hell, you'd probably get off on it.
-你为什么要不停的学别人讲话  -不  不对
What' did you rehearse this?  -No' no.
对像你这样的家伙来说这再好不过了
This was the best way for a guy like you.
慢慢来  放轻松些吧
Slow ticking clock, winding down.
这是必然的  无法妥协的  直到...
Inevitable, non-negotiable, until...
你他妈的到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?
你不知道吗?
你不知道吗？
-我想我开始明白了  -虽然迟点  但总好过永远不明白
I think I'm starting to figure it out.  -Better late than never.
你知道你会死在上面的
You know you're gonna die up there.
嗯  也许吧  但我会拉你垫背的
Yeah, maybe. But I'm taking you with me.
拿点药来  医生
Some pills' Doc.
你他妈的说什么?
Did you fucking say something?
-查略斯?  -你们好  女孩们
Chelios?  -Hello, girls.
站住
Hold up.
把枪给我
Give me the piece.
-你们两个真的是狼狈为奸啊?  -查略斯
Now, isn't that a fucking picture?  -Chelios.
你真是个可怕的东西
What a fucking nightmare you are.
别废话
No shit.
为什么不坐下来谈谈?
Sit down.
哇!  等等  你再搜一遍他
Whoa! Wait a minute. You pat him down, again.
我知道他肯定带了什么玩意儿
I know he's carrying something.
让我看看那东西
Let me see it.
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
聪明啊  这是什么  胰岛素泵?
Clever. What is this, an insulin pump?
差不多吧
Basically.
胰岛素是什么玩意儿?
What the fuck is insulin?
麻黄素  对吧?
Ephedrine' right?
-不错  -你真是足智多谋啊
Yeah.  -You're very resourceful.
-找到新老大了  小婊子?  -我可不是谁的婊子
Found a new master' little bitch?  -I'm nobody's bitch.
卡雷托付给你的钱只有我的一半  你就是个婊子
You'll be a bitch when Carlito hires you for half what he paid me.
够了
That's enough.
你会向你的老板摇尾乞怜  让他知道你是个多好的婊子
You'll throw boss a reach-around, show him you're a good bitch.
我可不是谁的婊子!
I'm nobody's little bitch!
你他妈的听明白了吗?
You fuckin' hear me?
-我要多少他就得付我多少!  -我说够了!
He'll pay what I tell him to pay!  -Enough!
坐下来!
Sit down!
这可真是多事的一天啊
It's been a long fucking day.
不管怎样  你必须承认  一切都干得很漂亮
In the end' you have to admit' it all works out quite nicely.
多亏了你  唐·金才死了
Don Kim gets his bullet, thanks to you,
也能给香港方面找到替罪羊
and Hong Kong gets a goat to take the fall.
-请你理解  这不是针对你个人的  -你只替你自己说好话
Please understand' it's nothing personal.  -Speak for yourself.
让我猜猜那是什么?
That what I think it is?
这就是中国的玩意儿
It's the Chinese shit.
按住他
Hold him down.
急什么  狗娘养的!
Not so fast, motherfucker!
他脑子坏了吧  唷!
He's gone dipsy-do, yo!
随你了  神经病
Whatever, psycho.
我的朋友  恐怕魔术师的表演该结束了
I'm afraid the Houdini act is over' my friend.
-我的天啊  谁他妈...  -闭嘴!
Our Father' who art in...  -Shut up!
那么  这是怎么回事
So, this is how it is.
-是唐·金!  他应该死了的!  -快
It's Don Kim! He's supposed to be dead!  -Presto.
警方已经包围了林特酒店
Police have moved to surround the Hotel Lint,
造成今天大混乱的疯狂男子
where the madman behind today's mayhem...
正藏匿在楼上做殊死挣扎
is holed up and making a desperate last stand.
官方已经证实  楼顶正发生枪战
Officials have confirmed gunfire on the sundeck.
我们会从酒店上方向您
Our news chopper will bring live,
进行全方位无删节现场直播
uncensored coverage from above the hotel.
重复一次  这次直播是无删节的
Again, this coverage is uncensored,
所以  请你们的小孩离开电视
so any small children present should leave the room.
把我救出去  快!
Get me out of here, now!
我要杀了你  查略斯!
I'll kill you' Chelios!
太晚了!
Too late!
小心!
Look out!
谢谢  老大
Thanks' boss.
让我们离开这鬼地方  快!  我们走!
Let's get the fuck out of here, now! Let's go!
凯洛的礼物
Present from Kaylo.
现在如何?  你就是坨屎!
Now what? Now you say shit!
你他妈的刚才在哪里?
Where the fuck were you?
现在谁是婊子?
Who's the bitch' now?
不  不!  你开飞机  狗娘养的!
No, no! You fly' motherfucker!
狗娘养的  起飞!
Motherfuckin' fly!
你死定了
You're dead!
啊  我的天!
Oh my God!
你死定了!  你死定了  狗娘养的!
You're dead' motherfucker!
我说了我会杀了你的  你个小婊子!
I told you I'd kill you' you little bitch!
嘿  我是伊芙  欢迎您来电  但是我现在不在
Hey, its Eve. I'm glad you called but I'm not here.
如果您不是推销员的话
Leave a message,
请给我留言
unless you're selling something 'cause I'm not interested.
如果是  我不会感兴趣的  那就...  等下  时间到了
If you're not, then just... Wait, time's up.
嘿  宝贝儿
Hey' doll...
看来我又让你失望了
Looks like I let you down' again.
看上去我这一生一直  只是在奔走...  奔走...
Seems like all my life I've just been going... going...
奔走...
going...
我真希望我能多点时间
I wish I'd taken more time...
可以说  能有空停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
...to stop and smell the roses' so to speak.
唔  我想现在说这些太迟了
Well' I guess it's too late for that now.
你是最棒的  宝贝儿
You're the greatest' baby.